<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Seattle Plastics</title>
    <link>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Seattle Plastics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gift Card Displays</title>
      <link>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/giftcarddisplays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/giftcarddisplays/</guid>
      <description>All displays can be modified for veritcal design gift cards. Call for more information.
 Product #100-300
3 Pocket Tiered Gift Card Display. Designed for space saving, this display has a small foot print, but delivers maximum results. Pocket width is 3.75&amp;quot;. Back sign holder is detachable and fits graphics that are 3.75&amp;quot; wide x 4&amp;quot; high. $16.00
 Product #100-400
4 pocket Tiered Gift Card Display with Sign Holder. Perfect for locations with limited space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chalkboard Signs</title>
      <link>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/chalkboardsigns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/chalkboardsigns/</guid>
      <description>Seattle Plastics is pleased to present our new line of plastic chalkboard products for the retail market.
Made from FDA approved acrylic, our items have a matte finish to mimic a chalkboard&amp;rsquo;s surface which can be fabricated into any product from slanted signs for deli cases, signs for bottle tops, gift card displays, tip jars and more. Unlike real chalkboard, it&amp;rsquo;s lightweight and cleans easily with any surface cleaner. Like chalkboard, it can be used with liquid chalk, dry erase pens, real chalk or new dry erase crayons from Crayola to create beautiful, professional sign holders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Fabrication</title>
      <link>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/customfabrication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/customfabrication/</guid>
      <description>With over 60% of our production dedicated to custom work, Seattle Plastics has developed manufacturing methods that can make your design a reality quickly and affordably.
Contact our sales team for a quote, or print and complete the fax sheet supplied below. We’ll need the following information to get started on your project:
 A rough sketch of your idea that includes dimensions Specific preferences, if any (such as colored acrylic or non-standard finishes) Quantities needed  A sales representative will respond quickly with price quotes and comments regarding the design and construction of your display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fulfillment Services</title>
      <link>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/fulfillmentservices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seattle-plastics-test.onrender.com/services/fulfillmentservices/</guid>
      <description>In addition to our complete line of stock items and custom work, Seattle Plastics offers fulfillment services.
We&amp;rsquo;re experienced in coordinating goods from multiple vendors. From literature to t-shirts, we can package your entire project so that it arrives safely at its final destination.
We can arrange all of the elements for a successful promotion, including:
 Product Labeling Silkscreen Imprinting Custom Packaging Insertion of Graphics and Brochures Kit Assembly Planned Promotional Roll-Outs by Date Stock Display Samples Custom Prototype Samples Nationwide Drop Shipment Expedited UPS Shipments Prompt Proof of Deliveries  Call us toll free at 1-800-441-0679 to find out how we can make your next project a little easier!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
